<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Marwadi Shaadi</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

    <string-array name="caste_array">
        <item>Maheshwari</item>
        <item>Agarwal</item>
        <item>Jain</item>
        <item>Khandelwal</item>
        <item>Others</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fstatus_array">
        <item>Select Family Status</item>
        <item>Affluent Class</item>
        <item>Upper Middle Class</item>
        <item>Middle Class</item>
        <item>Lower Middle</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="ftype_array">
        <item>Select Family Type</item>
        <item>Joint</item>
        <item>Nuclear</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="fvalues_array">
        <item>Select Family Values</item>
        <item>Orthodox</item>
        <item>Traditional</item>
        <item>Modern</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="diet_array">
        <item>Select Diet</item>
        <item>Jain</item>
        <item>Veg</item>
        <item>Non-Veg</item>
        <item>Eggetarian</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="smoking_array">
        <item>Do you smoke ? </item>
        <item>No</item>
        <item>Light</item>
        <item>Social</item>
        <item>Regular</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="drinking_array">
        <item>Do you drink ? </item>
        <item>No</item>
        <item>Light</item>
        <item>Social</item>
        <item>Regular</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="complexion_array">
        <item>Select Complexion</item>
        <item>Very Fair</item>
        <item>Fair</item>
        <item>Wheatish</item>
        <item>Wheatish Brown</item>
        <item>Dark</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="physicalstatus_array">
        <item>Select Physical Status</item>
        <item>Physically challenged from birth</item>
        <item>Physically challenged due to accident</item>
        <item>Mentally challenged from birth</item>
        <item>Mentally challenged due to accident</item>
        <item>Physically abnormality affecting only looks</item>
        <item>Physical abnormality affecting bodily functions</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="manglik_array">
        <item>Manglik ?</item>
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
        <item>Don\'t know</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="relation_name_array">
        <item>Your Relation is of ?</item>
        <item>Tauji</item>
        <item>Masaji</item>
        <item>Mamaji</item>
        <item>Nanaji</item>
        <item>Jijaji</item>
        <item>Fupaji</item>
        <item>Chachaji</item>
        <item>Bhuwaji</item>
        <item>Brother</item>
        <item>Sister</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="horoscope_array">
        <item>Match Horoscope ?</item>
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
        <item>Doesn\'t Matter</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="designation_array">
        <item>Select Designation</item>
        <item>Employee</item>
        <item>Director</item>
        <item>Founder</item>
        <item>Co-Founder</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="height_array">
        <item>Select Height</item>
        <item>4ft - 121 cm</item>
        <item>4ft - 121 cm</item>
        <item>4ft 1in - 124cm</item>
        <item>4ft 2in - 127cm</item>
        <item>4ft 3in - 129cm</item>
        <item>4ft 4in - 132cm</item>
        <item>4ft 5in - 134cm</item>
        <item>4ft 6in - 137cm</item>
        <item>4ft 7in - 139cm</item>
        <item>4ft 8in - 142cm</item>
        <item>4ft 9in - 144cm</item>
        <item>4ft 10in - 147cm</item>
        <item>4ft 11in - 149cm</item>
        <item>5ft - 152cm</item>
        <item>5ft 1in - 154cm</item>
        <item>5ft 2in - 157cm</item>
        <item>5ft 3in - 160cm</item>
        <item>5ft 4in - 162cm</item>
        <item>5ft 5in - 165cm</item>
        <item>5ft 6in - 168cm</item>
        <item>5ft 7in -170cm</item>
        <item>5ft 8in - 172cm</item>
        <item>5ft 9in - 175cm</item>
        <item>5ft 10in - 177cm</item>
        <item>5ft 11in - 180cm</item>
        <item>6ft - 182cm</item>
        <item>6ft 1in - 185cm</item>
        <item>6ft 2in - 187cm</item>
        <item>6ft 3in - 190cm</item>
        <item>6ft 4in - 193cm</item>
        <item>6ft 5in - 195cm</item>
        <item>6ft 6in - 198cm</item>
        <item>6ft 7in - 200cm</item>
        <item>6ft 8in - 203cm</item>
        <item>6ft 9in - 205cm</item>
        <item>6ft 10in - 208cm</item>
        <item>6ft 11in - 210cm</item>
        <item>7ft - 213cm</item>
        <item>7ft 1in - 215cm</item>
        <item>7ft 2in - 218cm</item>
        <item>7ft 3in - 221cm</item>
        <item>7ft 4in - 223cm</item>
        <item>7ft 5in - 226cm</item>
        <item>7ft 6in - 228cm</item>
        <item>7ft 7in - 231cm</item>
        <item>7ft 8in - 233cm</item>
        <item>7ft 9in - 236cm</item>
        <item>7ft 10in - 238cm</item>
        <item>7ft 11in - 241cm</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="aincome_array">
        <item>Select Annual Income</item>
        <item>Upto 300000</item>
        <item>300000 - 600000</item>
        <item>600000 - 1000000</item>
        <item>1000000 - 1500000</item>
        <item>1500000 - 2000000</item>
        <item>2000000 - 3000000</item>
        <item>2000000 - 3000000</item>
        <item>2000000 - 3000000</item>
        <item>2000000 - 3000000</item>
        <item>2000000 - 3000000</item>
        <item>3000000 - 5000000</item>
        <item>Above 5000000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="education_array">
        <item>Select Education</item>
        <item>Doctor</item>
        <item>Engineer</item>
        <item>CA/CS/ICWA</item>
        <item>MBA/MCA/MS/MA/MSC/M.Arch</item>
        <item>LLB/LLM</item>
        <item>Postgraduate</item>
        <item>Graduate</item>
        <item>Undergraduate</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="built_array">
        <item>Select Built</item>
        <item>Slim</item>
        <item>Athletic</item>
        <item>Average</item>
        <item>Heavy</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="status_array">
        <item>Select Marital Status</item>
        <item>Unmarried</item>
        <item>Widow</item>
        <item>Divorced</item>
        <item>Widower</item>
        <item>Seperated</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="facebook_app_id">1361344123954196</string>
    <string name="fb_login_protocol_scheme">fb1361344123954196</string>
    <string name="privacy1">Marwadishaadi.com is an online matrimonial portal endeavouring constantly to provide all Marwadis with premium matrimonial services under one roof. Our commitment to your right to privacy extends beyond this privacy statement wherein we value the information we collect from you and keep it completely confidential.</string>
    <string name="privacy2">We gather information from members and guests who apply for the matrimonial services our site offers. It includes email address, first name, last name, a user-specified password, mailing address, zip code and telephone number or fax number. Apart from these, we may also collect some detailed information about your interests and background to help you find a better match.</string>
    <string name="privacy3">We collect information from our clients primarily to ensure that we are able to fulfill your requirements and to deliver a personalised experience so that the matchmaking process becomes easier and fulfilling for you.</string>
    <string name="privacy4">The information collected from our clients is shared only with members of Marwadishaadi.com or members of our partners. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security. We are also bound to cooperate fully should a situation arise where we are required by law or legal process to provide information about a customer.</string>
    <string name="privacy5">The marwadishaadi.com team will contact you from time to time to acquaint you with various features and functionalities of the website. They will contact you for either "Service" or "Sales" through a variety of media like E-mail, SMS, MMS, Voice IVR, USSD, WAP messages, Telephonic Calls, etc. The calls made to you will be from a regular mobile or landline number which is not of the "140" series.</string>
    <string name="privacy6">We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments or as a result of a change of policy in our company. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Statement, please write in to admin@marwadishaadi.com</string>
    <string name="terms">1. Marwadi Shaadi Matrimonial Services is a partnership firm based in Thane, Mumbai\n\n2. Personal Details and Photos are not verified by the website on personal basis. Members/Users are  requested to make thorough inquiries before proceeding any further.\n\n3. Marwadi Shaadi would not be liable for any kind of claims / compensation arising out of post-marriage accidents, divorce or similar unfortunate events.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_advanced__signup__details">Advanced Signup Details</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="section_format">Hello World from section: %1$d</string>
    <string name="title_activity_navigation_drawer">NavigationDrawerActivity</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>
    <string name="title_activity_user_profile">UserProfile</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

</resources>
